/* eslint-disable prettier/prettier */
export const questions = [
    {
       "category":"Sport & Leisure",
       "id":"62399f2eaf96521963a08722",
       "correctAnswer":"Italy",
       "incorrectAnswers":[
          "Germany",
          "Argentina",
          "England"
       ],
       "question":"Which country won the 1934 FIFA World Cup, hosted in Italy?",
       "tags":[
          "sport"
       ],
       "type":"Multiple Choice",
       "difficulty":"medium",
       "regions":[
          
       ]
    },
    {
       "category":"Sport & Leisure",
       "id":"622a1c367cc59eab6f9500db",
       "correctAnswer":"Baby Pac-Man",
       "incorrectAnswers":[
          "Miss Pac-Man",
          "Mrs Pac-Man",
          "Super Pac-Man"
       ],
       "question":"What was the hybrid pinball/video game in the Pac-Man series?",
       "tags":[
          "sport"
       ],
       "type":"Multiple Choice",
       "difficulty":"medium",
       "regions":[
          
       ]
    },
    {
       "category":"Sport & Leisure",
       "id":"622a1c367cc59eab6f9500ca",
       "correctAnswer":"16",
       "incorrectAnswers":[
          "12",
          "10",
          "14"
       ],
       "question":"How many balls are on a pool table at the start of a game?",
       "tags":[
          "sport"
       ],
       "type":"Multiple Choice",
       "difficulty":"medium",
       "regions":[
          
       ]
    },
    {
       "category":"Sport & Leisure",
       "id":"622a1c367cc59eab6f950058",
       "correctAnswer":"Bantamweight",
       "incorrectAnswers":[
          "Heavyweight",
          "Lightweight",
          "Subweight"
       ],
       "question":"Which weight division in boxing lies between flyweight and featherweight?",
       "tags":[
          "boxing",
          "words",
          "sport"
       ],
       "type":"Multiple Choice",
       "difficulty":"medium",
       "regions":[
          
       ]
    },
    {
       "category":"Sport & Leisure",
       "id":"6242e80d8c2538f9601d2f8f",
       "correctAnswer":"The Gunners",
       "incorrectAnswers":[
          "The Posh",
          "The Bluebirds",
          "The Rams"
       ],
       "question":"What is the nickname of the English football team Arsenal?",
       "tags":[
          "football",
          "soccer",
          "uk",
          "london",
          "nicknames",
          "sport"
       ],
       "type":"Multiple Choice",
       "difficulty":"medium",
       "regions":[
          "GB",
          "FR",
          "IT",
          "DE",
          "BR",
          "MX",
          "ES",
          "AR",
          "NL",
          "BE"
       ]
    },
    {
       "category":"Sport & Leisure",
       "id":"622a1c347cc59eab6f94f8a6",
       "correctAnswer":"Motor Racing",
       "incorrectAnswers":[
          "Track and field",
          "Rowing",
          "Baseball"
       ],
       "question":"With which sport is Aryton Senna associated?",
       "tags":[
          "people",
          "sport"
       ],
       "type":"Multiple Choice",
       "difficulty":"medium",
       "regions":[
          
       ]
    },
    {
       "category":"Sport & Leisure",
       "id":"62417d640f96c4efe8d773c2",
       "correctAnswer":"New York Knicks",
       "incorrectAnswers":[
          "New York 76ers",
          "New York Penguins",
          "New York Eagles"
       ],
       "question":"Which of these is a basketball team based in New York?",
       "tags":[
          "sport"
       ],
       "type":"Multiple Choice",
       "difficulty":"medium",
       "regions":[
          
       ]
    },
    {
       "category":"Sport & Leisure",
       "id":"622a1c367cc59eab6f95008e",
       "correctAnswer":"Southpaw",
       "incorrectAnswers":[
          "Goofy",
          "Regular",
          "Orthodox"
       ],
       "question":"What Do You Call A Boxer Who Leads With Their Right? ",
       "tags":[
          "boxing",
          "sport"
       ],
       "type":"Multiple Choice",
       "difficulty":"medium",
       "regions":[
          
       ]
    },
    {
       "category":"Sport & Leisure",
       "id":"62417dc30f96c4efe8d773e7",
       "correctAnswer":"Toronto Blue Jays",
       "incorrectAnswers":[
          "Toronto Pelicans",
          "Toronto Sporting",
          "Toronto Blues"
       ],
       "question":"Which of these is a baseball team based in Toronto?",
       "tags":[
          "sport"
       ],
       "type":"Multiple Choice",
       "difficulty":"medium",
       "regions":[
          
       ]
    },
    {
       "category":"Sport & Leisure",
       "id":"6242e83aa22452794eaef20a",
       "correctAnswer":"The Irons",
       "incorrectAnswers":[
          "Cottagers",
          "The Hatters",
          "The Reds"
       ],
       "question":"What is the nickname of the English football team West Ham United?",
       "tags":[
          "sport"
       ],
       "type":"Multiple Choice",
       "difficulty":"medium",
       "regions":[
          
       ]
    }
 ]